#### Summary:

Currently finishing my Bachelors of Computer Science at Sam Houston State University. I am currently a contract worker specializing in JavaScript and web development and in my free time I work on various programming projects to hone my skills and learn new ones.

# Technologies / Skills

This is a non-exhaustive list of my most used technologies.

Languages	Frameworks	Tools	Databases
JavaScript	React	GIT	SQLite
HTML	Angular	NPM	MongoDB
CSS	Ionic Framework	APT	Redis
Java	Node.js	SCSS	
Python	Socket.io	Play Store	
	Android		

#### Experience

### Americans for Responsible Insurance – Technical Director, Chief Developer (May 2017 – Present)

In 2 months, I built a full stack app for users to gather information while going door-to-door. The project included the following parts:

- The app was written in Ionic 2
- The app could be deployed without manual update for the user, if there were any minor changes that needed to be done, they would occur as soon as the app was deployed instead of waiting on the app store
- The app uploads to a Node.js server with a simple POST request and saves the data to a REDIS database
- I used cron and nodemailer to send emails to clients at scheduled times

### Chad Jones Law Firm – Systems Administrator (January 2015 – December 2016)

Responsible for complete integrity of all devices and systems at the firm. Projects and tasks included:

- On call 24/7
- Contributed to the design of the new work spaces and completed their implementation for two new offices
- Worked on setup and placement of the primary on-site server
- In charge of all tiers of technical support on and off the campus
- Create documentation for proper procedures for all IT related projects
- In charge of technical purchases
- Primary advisor to the attorneys in matters of technology for their cases

### Education

#### BS of Software Engineering – Sam Houston State University (August 2016 – December 2018)

Acquired skills for teamwork and small projects for classes.

## Associate of Applied Science in Computer Science – Blinn College (2015)

Developed my passion for Computer Science, I learned the basics of programming and algorithm usage.

### **Eagle Scout and member of the Order of the Arrow**